The world is yours.
We Are Your Friends is a drama, music, romance film directed by Max Joseph.
Young Cole Carter dreams of hitting the big time as a Hollywood disc jockey, spending his days and
nights hanging with buddies and working on the one track that will set the world on fire.
Opportunity comes knocking when he meets James Reed, a
charismatic DJ who takes the 23-year-old under his wing.
Soon, his seemingly clear path to success gets complicated when he starts falling for his mentor's
girlfriend, jeopardizing his new friendship and the future he seems destined to fulfill.
Cole, played by Zac Efron.
James, played by Wes Bentley.
Sophie, played by Emily Ratajkowski.
Mason, played by Jonny Weston.
Ollie, played by Shiloh Fernandez.
Squirrel, played by Alex Shaffer.
We Are Your Friends is a 2015 drama film directed by Max Joseph (in his feature directorial debut) and
with a screenplay by Joseph and Meaghan Oppenheimer, from a story by Richard Silverman.
The film stars Zac Efron, Emily Ratajkowski and Wes Bentley, and follows a young Los Angeles DJ
trying to make it in the music industry and figure out life with his friends.
The film was released in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on August 28, 2015.
Its financier, StudioCanal, distributed it internationally, including France, the
United Kingdom, Germany, the Netherlands, Australia and New Zealand.
The film received mixed reviews and grossed $11 million.
The film explores themes of los angeles, california, san
fernando valley, duringcreditsstinger, dj.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.